Professional and personal papers of Edwin Wolf 2nd LCP.EW2
Library Company of Philadelphia
- III. Scholarship, Bulk, 1945-1988; 1833-1996
  - IIIb. Research, Bulk, 1945-1988; 1833-1996
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Gavleston. Original of Document [30], 1842 February 6 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Baltimore. Original of Document 31, 1842 November 30 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Rachel Lyons to Sarah Polock, on board Barque Calish; Hannah Dyer to Sarah Polock, on board Barque Calish. Original of Documents [32] and 33, 1843 November 9 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 34, 1843 December 9 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 35, 1844 April 17 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 36, 1844 December 26 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manusript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 37, 1845 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Galveston; Hannah Dyer to Sarah Polock. Original of Document 38, 1845 July 6 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 39, 1846 March 20 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 40, 1846 August 13 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 41, 1846 September 6 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Sarah to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of Document [42], 1847 February 17 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Lewis to Rebecca Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document [43], 1847 February 23 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Sarah to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of Document [44], 1847 July 30 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Sarah to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of document [45], 1847 July 30 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, Mexico. Original of Document [46], 1847 October 27 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Sarah to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of Document [47], 1848 January 21 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Moses Polock, New York. Original of Document [48], 1848 July 6 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Sarah to Moses Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document [49], 1848 September 20 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Moses Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document 50, 1848 November 29 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document 51, 1848 December 18 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document 52, 1848 December 30 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Lewis to Barnett Polock, Gorgona. Original of Document 53, 1849 January 8 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Sarah Polock, New Orleans. Original of Document 54, 1849 February 3 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Sarah to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 55, 1849 February 9 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Moses Polock, Panama. Original of Document 56, 1849 June 16 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, in ink, Barnett to Sarah Polock, San Francisco. Original of Document 57, 1849 July 27 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Sarah to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 58, 1849 August 3 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Polock papers, primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Barnett to Hyman Polock, Sacramento City, CA. Original of Document 59, 1849 September 15 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Abraham Dyer to Hyman Polock, San Francisco, University of California. Original of Document 61, 1849 October 29 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Polock papers, primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Sarah to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 62, 1849 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Sarah to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 63, 1849 December 2 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Hannah Dyer to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 64, 1849 December 13 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Abraham Dyer to Hyman Polock, San Francisco. Original of Document 65, 1850 January 31 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Lewis to Sarah Polock, Stockton. Original of Document 66, 1850 March 27 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Hannah Dyer to Moses Polock, Galveston. Original of Document 67, 1850 May 16 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Lewis to the Polock Family, San Francisco. Original of Document 68, 1850 October 14 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Lewis to Hyman Polock, San Francisco. Original of Document 69, 1851 January 1 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Solomon Polock to Isidore Binswanger, New Orleans. Original of Document 71, 1854 February 13 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Certificate, "It is hereby certified that Hyman Polock...Oct 20, 1824", 1824 October 20 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Joseph Osterman to Hyman Polock, Baltimore, 1830 September 3 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Peter Lamm to Hyman Polock, Dear Creek Mills [Clearfield County, PA], 1839 September 3 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Polock papers, primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed [in Yiddish-Deutch, with Hebrew phrases], M. S. Polock to Hyman Polock. Begins "Amsterdam, Eve of Yom Kippur, 5604", 1843 October 4 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Certificate, "It is hereby certifed that Miss Sarah Polock...25 May, 1860", 1860 May 25 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Rosanna Osterman to Miss S. Polock and Mrs. [J.?] Rosenbach, Galveston, 1865 May 3 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Rosanna Osterman to [Sarah Polock], Galveston, 1865 July 24 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Lease, signed by Sarah Polock and Matilda Cressman, for 614 Buttonwood St., 1871 July 18 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, S. Morais to Moses Polock, Cape Island, 1871 August 8 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Invitation, "Thirteenth birthday, Saturday evening, September 23rd, 1871..." (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, Isabella H. Rosenbach to Wm. B. Hackenburg, 1887 July 4 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter, signed, S. Morais to Sarah Polock, 1893 June 26 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Polock papers; primary source materials: Calling card, "Master Hyman P. Rosenbach", undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript letter and envelope [Hebrew text] to Hyman Pollack Rosenbach Esq., undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Mss, in 19th c. hand [?], "The First Hebrew Sunday School...", on stationery resembling that of the Ostermans, undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript [Hebrew], undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Manuscript notes in 19th c. [?] hand, undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Photograph, Hyman Pollock, circa 1865 (Box 3, Folder 74)
    - Polock papers; primary source material: Photograph, "Moses Polock", undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Polock papers, miscellaneous: Typed sheet, "The only significant acquisition since the last report...", undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Polock papers; miscellaneous: Typed letter, Mary Wolf to James Green, granting literary rights and unrestricted permission to the Library Company for publication of the Polock papers and related materials, 1995 January 25 (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Polock papers; miscellaneous: Typed letter, signed, Robert M. Peck to James Green, 1996 December 4 (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Captain General Alvara Saavedra: Typescript on Saavedra's explorations of the Americas, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Captain General Alvara Saavedra: Typescripts of the original sources used (11 items), undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Captain General Alvara Saavedra: Typescripts of the original sources used (11 items), undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Captain General Alvara Saavedra: Manuscript of an article on Saavedra, typescript excerpts from the Archivo de Indias, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Santo Domingo: Letters, newspaper clippings, tickets, and other materials from Edwin's trip to Haiti (19 items), 1934 January 25-March 13 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Santo Domingo: Letters, manuscripts (including poems), brochures and maps (12 items), 1934 April 4-1956 August (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Santo Domingo: Typescript of an unpublished article on Columbus, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Santo Domingo: Notes, manuscript, and typescript of an unpublished article entitled "True Land of Columbus" (6 items), undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Short Title Catalogue: Letters between Edwin and C. W. David and Mary C. Park; Mary C. Park's check on part of catalogue which Edwin found lacking, 1941 September 19-1942 December 10 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Short Title Catalogue: Correction by Edwin of Mary C. Park's check of catalogue as sent to University of Pennsylvania Chronicle; letters between Edwin and C. W. David, 1942 December 11-1943 December 18 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Short Title Catalogue: 5 letters between Edwin and Rittenhouse E. Neisser, W. Eisenberg, and W. W. Bishop; Edwin's checklist of the catalogue, 1943 January 29-1943 February 2 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Short Title Catalogue: Preliminary proposal by Foxon of Short Title Catalogue; letters between Edwin and Foxon, 1962 October (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - "Stinking or Skinking?: A Bibliographical Study": Research materials, typescript draft, reprint, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - U.S. emigrants: Transcriptions from 19th century sources relating to emigrants, undated (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Letter from Edwin to Charles F. Heartman, editor of American Book Collector, undated (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Unpublished autobiographical sketch intended for the William and Mary Quarterly for 1987, circa 1987 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Bibliographic descriptions of books owned by the Mathers, Franklins, and others, undated (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Bibliography of Edwin's published works, undated (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Letters between Edwin and P. Goodman and L. Given; review of Jane Mecom, Favorite Singer of Benjamin Franklin and The Letters of Benjamin Franklin and Jane Mecom, 1950 May 17-1952 March 10 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Counterfeit document purported to be by Sir Walter Raleigh, undated (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Loose leaves from an 18th century encyclopedia, undated (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Artwork for 1938 Free Library of Philadelphia exhibition "First Printers and Books", undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Illustration plate: "Men of the Day. No. 912", undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Illustration plate: Richard, First Earl of Howe, undated (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Photocopy of article on Sigmund Lubin, Betzwood, and the Philadelphia film industry, undated (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - National Geographic Magazine, 1951 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Article entitled “A Press for Penn's Pump,” Art Quarterly, XXIV, 227-248 [1961], with Robert C. Smith, circa 1961 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Photocopies of notes and various research files, undated (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Various notes regarding books, manuscripts, and some prices, undated (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Alan Pifer, "The Jeopardy of Private Institutions," 1970 Annual Report, Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Julian P. Boyd, "A Modest Proposal to Meet an Urgent Need," American Historical Review, 1965, circa 1965 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Roy F. Nichols, "History in a Self-Governing Culture," American Historical Review, 1967, circa 1967 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Whitfield J. Bell, Jr., "Painted Portraits and Busts in the American Philosophical Society," Antiques, 1973, circa 1973 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Robert Hay Carnie, "Boswell's Account of Corsica 1768," The Book Collector, 1977, circa 1977 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - James E. Walsh, "'The Librarian's Library': The William A. Jackson Bibliographical Collection," The Book Collector, 1965-1966, circa 1965 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Irving A. Beck, "An Early American Journal Keyed to Medical Students: A Pioneer Contribution of Elisha Bartlett," Bulletin of the History of Medicine, 1966, circa 1966 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Whitfield J. Bell, Jr., "A Potrait of the Colonial Physician: The Fielding H. Garrison Lecture," Bulletin of the History of Medicine, 1970 (2 copies), circa 1970 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Whitfield J. Bell, Jr., "Practitioners of History: Philadelphia Medical Historians Before 1925," Bulletin of the History of Medicine, 1976, circa 1976 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Eric T. Carlson and Meribeth M. Simpson, "Models of the Nervous System in Eighteenth Century Psychiatry," Bulletin of the History of Medicine, 1969, circa 1969 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Charles E. Rosenberg, "Inward Vision & Outward Glance: The Shaping of the American Hospital, 1880-1914," Bulletin of the History of Medicine, 1979, circa 1979 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Beverly P. Lynch, "Options for the 80s: Directions in Academic and Research Libraries," College & Research Libraries, 1982, circa 1982 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - David H. Stam, "'Prove All Things: Hold Fast That Which Is Good': Deaccessioning and Research Libraries," College & Research Libraries, 1982, circa 1982 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Norman S. Fiering, "Solomon Stoddard's Library at Harvard in 1664," Harvard Library Bulletin, 1972, circa 1972 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Owen Gingerich, "Rara Astronomica," Harvard Library Bulletin, 1971, circa 1971 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - Philip Hofer, "Preliminary Sketches for Gravelot's Cornielle," Harvard Library Bulletin, 1951, circa 1951 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - Robert F. Metzdorf, "The Publishing History of Richard Henry Dana's Two Years Before the Mast," Harvard Library Bulletin, 1953, circa 1953 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - Boies Penrose, "English Printing at Antwerp in the Fifteenth Century," Harvard Library Bulletin, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - Caroline Robbins, "Thomas Hollis in His Dorsetshire Retirement," Harvard Library Bulletin, 1975, circa 1975 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - Roger E. Stoddard, "The Use of Mourning Wrappers in New England, with a Note on Mourning Papers in English Books at Harvard," Harvard Library Bulletin, 1982, circa 1982 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Richard J. Wolfe, "A Footnote to the Publication of Peter Smith's Indian Doctor's Dispensatory (Cincinnati, 1813)," Harvard Library Bulletin, 1979, circa 1979 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - "Notes," Harvard Library Bulletin, 1950, circa 1950 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Eric T. Carlson and Meribeth M. Simpson, "Perkinism vs. Mesmerism," Journal of the History of the Behavioral Sciences, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Patricia S. Noel and Eric T. Carlson, "The Faculty Psychology of Benjamin Rush," Journal of the History of the Behavioral Sciences, 1973, circa 1973 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Michael H. Harris, "Books on the Frontier: The Extent and Nature of Book Ownership in Southern Indiana, 1800-1850," The Library Quarterly, 1972, circa 1972 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - Lee E. Grove, "John Murray and Paper Deterioration," Libri, 1966, circa 1966 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Lawrence Clark Powell, "The Power to Evoke," Manuscripts, 1953, circa 1953 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Justin G. Turner, "The Donner-Reed Party: Men Against Mountains, Salt, and Sand," Manuscripts, 1960, circa 1960 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Justin G. Turner, "The Five Manuscript Copies of the Gettysburg Address," Manuscripts, 1965, circa 1965 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Justin G. Turner, "General Dix and the American Flag," Manuscripts, 1969, circa 1969 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Summer 1989 issue of Manuscripts (Box 33, Folder 46)
    - Thomas R. Adams, "The Samuel J. Randall Papers," Pennsylvania History, Quarterly Journal of the Pennsylvania Historical Association, 1954, circa 1954 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Roger Butterfield, "George Lippard and His Secret Brotherhood," The Pennsylvania Magazine of History and Biography, 1955, circa 1955 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Edward C. Carter II, "A 'Wild Irishman' Under Every Federalist's Bed: Naturalization in Philadelphia, 1789-1806," The Pennsylvania Magazine of History and Biography, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - H. Trevor Colbourn, "John Dickinson, Historical Revolutionary," The Pennsylvania Magazine of History and Biography, 1959, circa 1959 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Lawrence Henry Gipson, "The Great Debate in the Committee of the Whole House of Commons on the Stamp Act, 1766, as Reported by Nathaniel Ryder," The Pennsylvania Magazine of History and Biography 1962, circa 1962 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Peter J. Parker, "Asbury Dickens, Bookseller, 1798-1801, or, The Brief Career of a Careless Youth," The Pennsylvania Magazine of History and Biography, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Whitfield J. Bell, Jr., "Rattlesnakes and Hummingbirds: Philadelphia's Resources for the History of Science," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Jacob Blanck, "The Star Spangled Banner," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1966, circa 1966 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Robert B. Brown, "Texans in Leopard Skin Pants," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1950, circa 1950 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Charles W. David, "The Longwood Library," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1957, circa 1957 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Alexander Davidson, Jr., "How Benson J. Lossing Wrote his 'Field Books' of the Revolution, the War of 1812 and the Civil War," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1938, circa 1938 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Richard Beale Davis, "Sandy's Song of Solomon: Its Manuscript Versions and Their Circulation," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1956, circa 1956 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Frederick R. Goff, "The Dates in Certain German Incunabula," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1940, circa 1940 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Frederick R. Goff, "The Preparation of the Third Census of Incunabula in American Libraries," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1970, circa 1970 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Robert F. Metzdorf, "Bibliographical Notes:The First American 'Rasselas' and Its Imprint," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1953, circa 1953 (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Ted-Larry Pebworth, "Sir Henry Wotton's 'Dazel'd Thus, with Height of Place' and the Appropriation of Political Poetry in the Earlier Seventeenth Century," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1977, circa 1977 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Gordon N. Ray, "The Changing World of Rare Books," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1965, circa 1965 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Leona Rostenberg, "The Printers of Strassburg and Humanism, from 1501 until the Advent of the Reformation," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1940, circa 1940 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Roger E. Stoddard, "C. Fiske Harris, Collector of American Poetry and Plays," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1963, circa 1963 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Roger E. Stoddard, "Bibliographical Notes: Some Corrigenda and Addenda to Hill's American Plays Printed 1714-1830," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1971, circa 1971 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Roger E. Stoddard, "Lost Books: American Poetry before 1821," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1982, circa 1982 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Roger E. Stoddard, "Vanity and Reform: B. O. Flower's Arena Publishing Company, Boston, 1890-1896. With a Bibliographical List of Arena Imprints," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1982, circa 1982 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - David M. Vieth, "The Text of Rochester and the Editions of 1680," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1956 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - David M. Vieth, "Order of Contents as Evidence of Authorship: Rochester's Poems of 1680," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1959, circa 1959 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - David M. Vieth, "A Textual Paradox: Rochester's 'To a Lady in a Letter'," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1960, circa 1960 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - David M. Vieth, "Bibliographical Notes: A Unsuspected Cancel in Tonson's 1691 'Rochester'," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1961, circa 1961 (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - John Cook Wyllie, "The Forms of Twentieth-Century Cancels," Papers of the Bibliographical Society of America, 1953, circa 1953 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Rudolf Hirsch, "The Art of Selling Books: Notes on Three Aldus Catalogues, 1586-1592," Papers of the Bibliographical Society, University of Virginia, 1949, undated (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Allan H. Stevenson, "New Uses of Watermarks as Bibliographical Evidence," Papers of the Bibliographical Society, University of Virginia, 1949, undated (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Gordon M. Marshall, "Americana in the Scheide Library: Adventures of a Novice," The Princeton University Chronicle, 1976, circa 1976 (Box 34, Folder 30)